(Howard:)Mostly with Asian
and Jewish astronauts.
(Penny:)All right. Pass the soy sauce.
Coming up.
(Leonard:)So how's work?
(Penny:)Oh, it's not bad.
(Penny:)Kind of hungry.
(Leonard:)Yeah, we all are.
(Howard:)Just wait.
(Sheldon:)You realize, Penny,
that the technology
(Sheldon:)that went into this arm
will one day make
(Sheldon:)unskilled food servers
such as yourself obsolete.
(Penny:)Really?
(Penny:)They're going to make a robot
that spits on your hamburger?
(Sheldon:)I thought you
broke up with her.
(Sheldon:)Why is she here?
(Howard:)Okay, here we go.
(Howard:)Passing the soy sauce.
(Howard:)Put out your hand.
Oh!
(Penny:)That's amazing.
(Sheldon:)I wouldn't say amazing.
(Sheldon:)At best,
it's a modest leap forward
(Sheldon:)from the basic technology
(Sheldon:)that gave us
Country Bear Jamboree.
(Howard:)Hey, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Yes?
(Sheldon:)Peace?
(Howard:)No, not peace.
(Howard:)Hang on.